Bel Canto is a drama, music, romance film directed by Paul Weitz.
A famous opera singer is held hostage in South America by a guerrilla rebel group
after performing at a Japanese businessman's lavish birthday party.
Unexpected bonds are forged in the standoff that ensues.
Roxanne Cross, played by Julianne Moore.
Katsumi Hosokawa, played by Ken Watanabe.
Messner, played by Sebastian Koch.
Gen, played by Ryo Kase.
Comandante Benjamin ( Benjas), played by Tenoch Huerta Mejía.
Comandante Alfredo, played by Noé Hernández.
Bel Canto is a 2018 American drama film directed by Paul Weitz,
from a screenplay by Weitz and Anthony Weintraub.
It is based on the 2001 novel of the same name by Ann Patchett.
It stars Julianne Moore, Ken Watanabe, Sebastian Koch, and Christopher Lambert.
It was released on September 14, 2018 by Screen Media Films.
The tone is emotional and intense.